[With English subtitles]
[有英文字幕]
[Spy Game]
[间谍游戏]
[Episode 17]
[第17集]
Why did Fang Lu suddenly
方璐怎么突然
Investigate his father?
调查他的父亲？
Chen Ting says
陈婷说
Because Zheng Guoxian was suddenly arrested,
因为郑国贤突然被捕，
This angered him.
这激怒了他。
what should we do
我们应该做什么
do it now?
现在做？
Fang Yongping promised
Fang Yongping promised
Let Fang Lu go abroad.
让方璐出国。
As long as Fang Lu leaves,
只要方璐离开，
He will not turn himself in.
他不会自首。
Fang Lu will not leave.
方璐不会走。
He is not the one with the final say.
他不是拥有最终决定权的人。
We must protect Fang Yongping.
We must protect Fang Yongping.
Dispose
处置
Fang Lu has all the evidence.
方璐所有的证据都有。
We cannot leave any clues to the national security.
我们不能给国安留下任何线索。
knew.
知道了。
[Prosperity, democracy, civilization, harmony]
【繁荣、民主、文明、和谐】
[Freedom, equality, justice, rule of law]
【自由、平等、正义、法治】
[Patriotism, dedication, integrity, friendliness]
【爱国、敬业、诚信、友善】
Come in.
进来。
Mayor Fang,
Mayor Fang,
what can I do for you?
我能为你做什么？
go
去
and help me
并帮助我
put it together
放在一起
the following few days
接下来的几天
and crimp it.
并压接它。
I'll review it.
我会审查一下。
OK
好的。
When do you need it?
你什么时候需要它？
as soon as possible.
尽快地。
do you have any plans
你有什么计划吗
the following few days
接下来的几天
Sort of.
有点。
[Strengthen four consciousnesses]
【强化四个意识】
【God helps those who help themselves】
【天助自助者】
【Yunshang Art Museum】
【云上美术馆】
[Closed today]
[今日休息]
what are you doing here?
你在这里做什么？
Fang Lu,
Fang Lu,
can we talk?
我们可以谈谈吗？
I have nothing to say to you.
我跟你没什么可说的。
Don't you want to know the truth?
你不想知道真相吗？
I already know the truth.
我已经知道真相了。
There are things you don't know.
有一些你不知道的事情。
Please calm down.
请冷静下来。
Do I look impulsive?
我看起来很冲动吗？
Is this a good approach?
这是一个好方法吗
Solve the problem
解决问题
Send it to your father
送你父亲
go to jail?
进监狱？
What did he tell you?
他告诉你的？
within a few years,
几年内，
He will retire,
他将退休，
Why can't you let him go?
你为什么不能放他走？
Shouldn't he be punished?
他不应该受到惩罚吗
Because it's illegal?
因为违法？
And you.
你呢。
You can't escape either.
你也无法逃脱。
sometimes,
有时，
We have no choice.
我们别无选择。
Stop pretending to be innocent
别再装无辜了
OK?
好的？
do you remember
你是否记得
The story you told me?
你告诉我的故事？
You said you started from scratch.
你说你从头开始。
Then, your business fails.
然后，你的生意就失败了。
but you used
但你用过
your persistence
你的坚持
Build your career
成就你的事业
Step by step.
一步步。
Now that I think about it,
现在我想起来，
Your story is just a joke.
你的故事只是一个笑话。
This is no joke.
这可不是说笑。
this is all
这就是全部
My personal experience.
我的个人经历。
if i didn't
如果我没有
Business failure,
生意失败，
I might
我可能
Won't be here today.
今天不会在这里。
then,
当时，
I spent all my savings
我花光了所有的积蓄
Do business abroad.
到国外做生意。
I did not expect
我没想到
Got screwed.
被搞砸了。
All I had was a warehouse full of unsold wine.
我所拥有的只是一个装满未售出葡萄酒的仓库。
I'm so desperate
我是如此绝望
So much so that when I was about to give up
以至于我快要放弃的时候
Fortunately,
幸运的是，
I met someone who could help me.
我遇到了一个可以帮助我的人。
He can save my life
他能救我的命
Help me return to Jinhai
帮我回金海
And do what I want.
并做我想做的事。
[Legal representative: Chen Ting]
【法定代表人：陈婷】
Pay the price by doing small things,
通过做一些小事而付出代价，
I can take this opportunity.
我可以抓住这个机会。
do you know
你知道吗
Why did they choose me?
他们为什么选择我？
because
因为
I know your father.
我认识你父亲。
then,
当时，
I would love to get the money I lost back.
我很想拿回我损失的钱。
So, I looked around for connections.
于是，我四处寻找联系。
I met Fang Yongping,
I met Fang Yongping,
who is the director
谁是导演
In the development zone.
在开发区。
He pitied me
他可怜我
And helped me find the scammer.
并帮我找到了骗子。
But the crook ran away.
但骗子却跑掉了。
There is nothing the Public Security Bureau can do.
公安局也无能为力。
But I am really grateful to Yong Ping.
但我真的很感谢永平。
So the way you thank him is
所以你感谢他的方式就是
Involve him?
让他参与进来？
You think too highly of me.
你对我评价太高了。
what happened to him
他发生了什么事情
It's beyond my control.
超出了我的控制范围。
Apart from,
除了，
I helped him a lot.
我帮了他很多。
Don't beautify yourself.
不要美化自己。
people like you
像你这样的人
can do anything
可以做任何事
achieve your goals.
达到您的目的。
You can hate me,
你可以恨我，
And look down on me.
并且看不起我。
but you shouldn't
但你不应该
Hate your father.
讨厌你的父亲。
For me at that time,
对于当时的我来说，
The most important thing is to turn losses into profits.
最重要的是扭亏为盈。
But for him,
但对他来说，
save you
拯救你
is the most important.
是最重要的。
[Quiet]
[安静]
I know
我知道
My son is fine.
我儿子很好。
No matter how playful he is,
不管他多么贪玩，
He would never break the law.
他永远不会违法。
tell me.
告诉我。
Do you
你是否
Set these things up?
设置这些东西？
Do you want to mess with me?
你想惹我吗？
What do you mean?
你是什​​么意思？
Who are you?
你是谁？
listen,
听，
You can expose the news however you want.
你可以随心所欲地曝光新闻。
I don't buy it.
我不买。
We just want to work with you.
我们只是想与您合作。
You are not our only option.
你不是我们唯一的选择。
but if you want your son
但如果你想要你的儿子
Come back alive,
活着回来，
we may be
我们可能是
Your only choice.
你唯一的选择。
If I knew the price was like this
如果我知道价格是这样的话
I'd rather have nothing then.
我宁愿那时什么都没有。
Fang Lu,
Fang Lu,
please
请
Spare everyone's life.
饶恕大家的生命。
Don't be so cruel.
别这么残忍。
Can you stop running away from what's happening?
你能停止逃避所发生的事情吗？
With everything that happened,
随着发生的一切，
Do you think I have no doubts at all?
你以为我根本就没有怀疑过吗？
Because I ran away,
因为我逃跑了，
it got
它得到了
So far.
至此。
Is escaping useful?
逃跑有用吗？
That's not running away. this is protection
那不是逃跑。这就是保护
your life
你的生命
It's the spy agency's biggest bargaining chip
是间谍机构最大的筹码
to threaten him.
来威胁他。
To protect you,
为了保护你，
He couldn't stop it.
他无法阻止它。
do you know
你知道吗
Spy agency?
间谍机构？
If you insist,
如果你坚持，
they will
他们会
Kill you at any time.
随时杀掉你。
So you're here to threaten me?
所以你是来威胁我的？
Don't you want to know the truth?
你不想知道真相吗？
I'm here to tell you the truth.
我来这里是为了告诉你真相。
This is a fact.
这是事实。
Did you finish it?
你做完了吗？
leave.
离开。
【Sculpture and Touch】
【雕塑与触摸】
[Place an order in time]
【及时下单】
[Chris Chen]
[克里斯·陈]
future.
未来。
Fang Lu’s flashing dick
方璐的闪光鸡巴
Read it a minute ago.
一分钟前读过。
are you sure?
你确定吗？
Can't go wrong.
不会错的。
Huang Zicheng Implantation Procedure
黄子成植入程序
Has reminder function
具有提醒功能
In Fang Lu’s U disk.
方璐的U盘里。
Where does the extraction happen?
提取发生在哪里？
At his house.
在他家。
Fang Lu's house?
Fang Lu's house?
Isn’t it Fang Lu and Chen Ting?
方璐和陈婷不是吗
Meeting at an art gallery?
在美术馆见面？
Someone went to Fang Lu's house
有人去了方璐家
Destroy evidence.
销毁证据。
Huang Zicheng put a GPS device
Huang Zicheng put a GPS device
in a flash drive.
在闪存盘中。
This man has thrown himself into a trap.
这个人已经把自己扔进了陷阱。
We are getting closer.
我们正在接近目标。
The target is Pinghai Road.
目标是平海路。
I saw him.
我看到了他。
It's that motorcycle again.
又是那辆摩托车。
His back looks familiar.
他的背影看起来很熟悉。
This is the same person.
这是同一个人。
Drive slower. Don't follow the target too closely.
开车慢点。不要太紧密地跟随目标。
What is that place?
那是什么地方？
Gimhae International Racing Club.
金海国际赛车俱乐部。
What is he doing here?
他在这里做什么？
Is he a racing driver?
他是赛车手吗？
Or a coach?
还是教练？
Get out of the car and take a look.
下车看看吧。
[No fireworks allowed]
【禁止燃放烟花爆竹】
Why are there so many people here?
为什么这里有这么多人？
Is there a competition?
有比赛吗？
look.
看。
The signal is gone.
信号没了。
Let's go in.
我们进去吧。
can I help you?
我可以帮你吗？
hello i want to know
你好，我想知道
Why are there so many people outside?
外面怎么这么多人？
Is there competition?
有竞争吗？
every Wednesday,
每个星期三，
Our club will be holding night games.
我们俱乐部将举行夜间比赛。
Can we go in?
我们可以进去吗？
Are you a member?
你是会员吗？
No, I am not.
不，我不是。
sorry.
对不起。
We only serve members.
我们只为会员服务。
I understand.
我懂了。
Sorry to bother you.
很抱歉打扰你。
-It doesn't matter. -goodbye
-没关系。-再见
No progress today.
今天没有任何进展。
Don't expose ourselves. let's go.
不要暴露我们自己。我们走吧。
[No fireworks allowed]
【禁止燃放烟花爆竹】
us
我们
Let him run away again.
让他再次逃跑。
he is very familiar
他很熟悉
and seminars.
与研讨会。
I don't think he's a racing driver.
我不认为他是赛车手。
He doesn't have to worry
他不必着急
Participate in the competition.
参加比赛。
More likely he was a staff member.
他更有可能是一名工作人员。
What's wrong?
怎么了？
depressed.
郁闷。
But that's not the worst outcome.
但这还不是最坏的结果。
at least you know
至少你知道
He will be at the club.
他将出现在俱乐部。
Are you comforting me?
你在安慰我吗？
No, I'm just reminding you.
不，我只是提醒你。
It's impossible to win every time.
不可能每次都赢。
That's more like what you would say.
这更像是你会说的。
We must always be patient.
我们必须始终保持耐心。
He is a formidable opponent.
他是一个强大的对手。
But I will find him.
但我会找到他。
I trust you.
我相信你。
Fanglu’s USB flash drive
方路的U盘
has been disposed of.
已被处置。
what have you done
你做了什么
give him?
给他？
how so?
怎么会这样？
he does not know.
他不知道。
flash drive T
闪存盘T
It doesn't matter anymore.
不再重要了。
As long as he has no evidence,
只要他没有证据，
He won't force you anymore.
他不会再强迫你了。
But he discovered the truth
但他发现了真相
His father was a spy.
他的父亲是一名间谍。
Nothing to do with this
与此无关
with whether he still
与他是否仍然
There is conclusive evidence
有确凿的证据
In his hands.
在他的手中。
do you understand?
你明白吗？
Yongping,
Yongping,
we can send him abroad
我们可以把他送到国外
buy him a gallery
给他买一个画廊
or something else
或者是其他东西
let him do it
让他做
He does whatever he wants.
他想做什么就做什么。
even if he can't
即使他不能
Get to know you in a short time.
短时间内了解你。
But blood relationship
但血缘关系
between you and him
你和他之间
It can never be erased.
永远无法被抹去。
sooner or later,
迟早，
he will understand
他会明白的
everything you do now
你现在所做的一切
It's for his own good.
是为了他好。
if i do
如果我这样做的话
he will never
他永远不会
sorry.
对不起。
but have you ever thought about
但你有没有想过
who can protect him
谁能保护他
What if you bring yourself in?
如果你把自己带进去？
But if I do what they want me to do
但如果我做他们想让我做的事
Send your son abroad
送儿子出国
And I continued in this position,
并且我继续保持在这个位置，
Then I must
那我必须
Be their puppet forever.
永远成为他们的傀儡。
they could use my son
他们可以使用我的儿子
threaten me
威胁我
do it
去做
I don’t want to do it anytime.
我什么时候都不想做。
Have you thought it through?
你想清楚了吗？
you want to give up everything
你想要放弃一切
What are you working so hard for?
你这么努力是为了什么？
Put myself in it.
把我自己交进去。
I must surrender.
我必须自首。
As long as I surrender
只要我自首
Can this all end?
这一切都可以结束吗。
And my son Fang Lu,
还有我的儿子方路，
can start a new life
可以开始新的生活
On his own terms.
按照他自己的条件。
this might be
这可能是
The last time we met.
我们最后一次见面。
I know
我知道
you work for them,
你为他们工作，
You have your difficulties too.
你也有你的困难。
if you can,
如果可以的话，
Please leave as soon as possible.
请尽快离开。
Go further away
走远点吧
that's all i can do
这就是我能做的一切
For you.
为你。
【He has made up his mind. 】
【他已经下定决心了。】
We have
我们有
Racing clubs were investigated.
调查了赛车俱乐部。
Yunyi Group
Yunyi Group
is one of their shareholders.
是他们的股东之一。
in other words,
换句话说，
Chen Ting is easy
陈婷很容易
arrange someone
安排某人
On her own side.
她自己这边的。
It's Yun Yi again.
又是云逸。
Chen Ting's business
陈婷的生意
there's a lot to do
有很多事要做
With night fog.
与夜雾。
Fang Yongping provides political guarantee
方永平提供政治保障
help
帮助
The development of Yunyi Group.
云亿集团的发展。
Yunyi Group
Yunyi Group
Give full play to industrial advantages
发挥产业优势
Go help Ye Wu.
去帮助夜雾。
Government colludes with businessmen
政府与商人勾结
Provide convenience and protection
提供便利和保护
espionage for night fog
用于夜雾的间谍活动
in Jinhai.
in Jinhai.
This is a big net.
这是一张大网。
Director Qin,
秦主任，
Take a look.
看一看。
All information is available
所有的信息都有
In Fang Lu’s U disk.
方璐的U盘里。
we have checked
我们已经检查过了
with professionals,
与专业人士，
and found Fang Yongping
and found Fang Yongping
Took Chen Ting’s money
拿了陈婷的钱
Through Fang Lu’s overseas account.
通过方璐的海外账户。
Recent remittances
最近的汇款
was to Zheng Guoxian.
was to Zheng Guoxian.
Please take a seat.
请坐。
Fang Lu’s account
方璐的账号
It can only prove that he has financial connections
只能证明他有经济联系
with Chen Ting and Zheng Guoxian.
with Chen Ting and Zheng Guoxian.
It does not prove that all this is related to Fang Yongping.
并不能证明这一切都与方永平有关。
After a series of searches,
经过一系列的搜寻，
The evidence again points to Fang Lu and Chen Ting.
证据再次指向方璐和陈婷。
Fang Yongping remained indifferent to the matter.
方永平对此事保持冷漠。
Can we accept what happened between Fang Yongping and Chen Ting?
方永平和陈婷的事情我们能接受吗
As a breakthrough?
作为突破？
It's just an immoral way to live.
这只是一种不道德的生活方式。
we need to investigate
我们需要调查
what Fang Yongping
what Fang Yongping
Made for spy agencies.
为间谍机构做的。
We can talk to Fang Lu.
我们可以和方路谈谈。
Now that he has discovered
既然他已经发现了
the truth,
真相，
Maybe he'd like to admit to the whole thing?
也许他愿意承认整个事件？
[Quiet]
[安静]
【Full of courage】【Maturity of life】
【充满魄力】【人生的成熟】
Fang Yongping has participated in many activities.
方永平参与过很多活动。
If he surrenders
如果他自首的话
A lot of people will be involved.
很多人都会参与其中。
I won't let him turn himself in.
我不会让他自首的。
try it.
尝试一下。
Do you like it?
你喜欢它？
Miss Zhang sent me a message
张小姐给我发消息
Ask why you haven't started working yet.
询问你为什么还没有开始工作。
I have no idea.
我不知道。
There is no use worrying.
担心是没有用的。
I told her.
我告诉她了。
Fang Lu hasn't
Fang Lu hasn't
Have you contacted me recently?
最近联系过你吧？
I would like to know
我想知道
How is his investigation going?
他的调查进展如何。
Fang Lu.
Fang Lu.
Hello.
你好。
i know why
我知道为什么
you insist
你坚持
About help me.
关于帮助我。
Now,
现在，
I think I'm stuck
我想我被困住了
inside.
在里面。
do you understand me?
你懂我的意思吗？
I really want to go back to the past
我真的很想回到过去
When I don't know anything.
当我什么都不知道的时候。
This is... this is...
这是……这是……
It's really hard for me right now.
现在对我来说真的很难。
Where are you?
你在哪里？
Why is it so noisy there?
那里怎么这么吵？
listen to me,
听我说，
I feel terrible.
我感觉糟透了。
I really can't? ? ?
我真的不能？？？
I can't take it anymore, man.
我再也受不了了，兄弟。
Hello? Hello?
你好？你好？
what did he say?
他说什么？
Fang Lu
Fang Lu
It seemed like I was drunk in a bar.
好像在酒吧喝醉了。
Let's go and see.
我们去看看吧。
let's go.
我们走吧。
A glass of whiskey.
一杯威士忌。
[free shipping]
[免运费]
where is he?
他在哪里？
here.
这里。
Fang Lu.
Fang Lu.
How much did he drink?
他喝了多少酒？
I feel something is wrong.
我觉得有些不对劲。
Fang Lu.
Fang Lu.
I'll call an ambulance.
我会叫救护车。
【Justice and Discipline】
【正义与纪律】
I received a notification from Team 1
我收到一号队的通知
Fang Lu fainted in the bar.
方璐在酒吧晕倒。
what happened?
发生了什么？
We don't know the details.
我们不知道细节。
They just said he passed out at the bar.
他们只是说他在酒吧晕倒了。
Where is he now?
他现在在哪儿？
On the way to the hospital.
去医院的路上。
By the way, Huang Zicheng was also present.
对了，黄子成也在场。
Huang Zicheng?
Huang Zicheng?
Yes, he went later.
是的，他后来去了。
When he arrived,
当他到达时，
Fang Lu had passed out.
方璐已经昏过去了。
listen,
听，
I'm going to the hospital now.
我现在要去医院。
You take some men to a bar.
你带一些男人去酒吧。
OK
好的。
Jiang, come with me.
蒋，跟我来吧。
what happened?
发生了什么？
Fang Lu fainted in the bar.
方璐在酒吧晕倒了。
【Justice and Discipline】
【正义与纪律】
【Loyalty and Skills】
【忠诚与技能】
[Emergency surgery]
[急诊手术]
【Emergency Internal Medicine】
【急诊内科】
[Upper gastrointestinal bleeding rescue channel]
【上消化道出血抢救通道】
【Observatory】
【观察室】
【Central operating room】
【中央手术室】
Uncle Fang.
方叔叔。
Did it? ? ?
做过？？？
Did you send him here?
你把他派到这里来吗？
He is undergoing examination.
他正在接受检查。
I don't know what happened to him.
我不知道他怎么样了。
Who are you?
你是谁？
We are Fang Lu’s friends.
我们是方璐的朋友。
[Green Channel for Stroke Chest Pain]
【中风胸痛绿色通道】
[Upper gastrointestinal bleeding rescue channel]
【上消化道出血抢救通道】
when we found him in the bar
当我们在酒吧找到他时
He has lost consciousness.
他已经失去知觉了。
I guess...
我猜测...
We suspect this is
我们怀疑这是
Alcoholism.
酒精中毒。
[Green Channel for Stroke Chest Pain]
【中风胸痛绿色通道】
[Upper gastrointestinal bleeding rescue channel]
【上消化道出血抢救通道】
Who is Fang Lu's family?
方禄的家人是谁？
[Emergency Department]
[急诊科]
[Green Channel for Stroke Chest Pain]
【中风胸痛绿色通道】
[Upper gastrointestinal bleeding rescue channel]
【上消化道出血抢救通道】
I am.
我是。
The test results are out.
测试结果出来了。
Please go to room 3.
请到3号房间。
[Emergency Department]
[急诊科]
keep going.
继续前进。
OK, thanks.
好的谢谢。
[Green Channel for Stroke Chest Pain]
【中风胸痛绿色通道】
[Upper gastrointestinal bleeding rescue channel]
【上消化道出血抢救通道】
I'll take care of Fang Lu.
我来照顾方璐。
Thanks.
谢谢。
I think Fang Lu is in danger.
我觉得方璐有危险了。
What do you want to say?
你想说什么？
Do you think someone tried to kill him?
你认为有人试图杀他吗？
what do you think?
你怎么认为？
I don't believe this was an accident.
我不相信这是一次意外。
then why do you
那你为什么
Stop me from telling the truth?
阻止我说实话？
because
因为
We cannot expose ourselves.
我们不能暴露自己。
Mayor Fang
Mayor Fang
Participation in this event is required.
必须参与该事件。
he knows
他知道
More than us.
比我们多。
if he deems it necessary
如果他认为有必要的话
He would call the police himself.
他会亲自报警。
That makes sense.
这就说得通了。
let's go.
我们走吧。
We found that the stimulant content exceeded the legal limit
我们发现兴奋剂成分超标
in the patient's blood.
在病人的血液中。
This makes him
这让他
Insanity.
精神失常。
This is impossible.
这不可能。
my son never
我儿子从来没有
take medicine.
服用药物。
Regardless of whether he suffered it himself or not
不管是不是他自己承受的
or forced,
或被迫，
I suggest you call the police.
我建议你报警。
After all, this stimulant
毕竟这种兴奋剂
Prohibited
被禁止
And addictive.
并且令人上瘾。
What's wrong?
怎么了？
You analyzed it
你分析了一下
It was peaceful just now.
刚才很平静。
I didn't think too much
我没有想太多
in hospital.
在医院。
Now I feel this
现在我觉得这件事
It must be related to Ms. Zhang.
肯定和张女士有关系。
but why do they
但他们为什么
do so to Fang Lu?
do so to Fang Lu?
These bastards.
这些混蛋。
Do you think
你认为
Ms. Zhang already knows
张女士已经知道了
Have we contacted Fang Lu?
我们联系方路了吗？
Has she contacted you recently?
她最近联系过你吗？
No.
不。
Don't worry. I'm here.
不用担心。我在这。
If Ms. Zhang
如果张女士
Found out we played a trick
发现我们玩了把戏
secretly,
偷偷，
we will eventually
我们最终会
like Fang Lu.
like Fang Lu.
[Spy Game]
[间谍游戏]
[Arrived at the designated location]
【到达指定地点】
[track]
[追踪]
[Teacher Zhang, see you where you are. 】
【张老师，我们原地见。】
Miss Zhang wants to meet me.
张小姐想见见我。
does she have
她有吗
find us?
找到我们？
she may be
她可能是
Just now at the bar.
刚才在酒吧。
what should we do
我们应该做什么
do it now?
现在做？
We need to solve it first.
我们需要先解决它。
【02Emergency】
【02紧急情况】
[Chen Ting, I’ll wait for you outside. 】
【陈婷，我在外面等你。】
[locker room]
[更衣室]
【One patient in one room】
【一室一病人】
Is Fang Lu feeling better?
方璐好点了吗？
Who did it?
谁干的？
sorry.
对不起。
I did not expect
我没想到
event.
事件。
Who did this?
这是谁做的？
I have no idea.
我不知道。
They just want me to tell? ? ?
他们只是想让我告诉？？？
you did it.
你做到了。
not me.
不是我。
tell me!
告诉我！
that's not me!
那不是我！
How did they know?
他们是怎么知道的？
you poisoned my son
你毒害了我儿子
Right under my nose.
在我眼皮底下。
do you want me
你想要我吗
Risking my life with you?
和你一起冒生命危险吗？
Yongping, I swear.
永平，我发誓。
I don't know what happened
我不知道发生了什么
Until just now.
直到刚才。
I did not expect
我没想到
This will happen.
这将会发生。
Can you calm down?
你能冷静点吗？
My son is in a coma.
我儿子处于昏迷状态。
tell me,
告诉我，
How can I calm down?
我怎样才能冷静下来？
Even if you kill me now
就算你现在杀了我
it's useless.
没用的。
Can you
你可以吗
state your position
表明你的立场
On the side.
在一边。
our top priorities
我们的首要任务
It was to save Fang Lu.
是为了救方璐。
what do you want?
你想要什么？
they just want me to tell you
他们只是想让我告诉你
You should never consider turning yourself in.
你永远不应该考虑自首。
Are you and Fang Lu
你和方璐是
under their watch.
在他们的监视下。
you
你
Harming my son right under my nose.
在我眼皮子底下伤害我的儿子。
do you expect me
你期待我吗
Cooperate with you?
与你合作？
Yongping,
Yongping,
We have no choice.
我们别无选择。
Fang Lu is in a coma.
方璐处于昏迷状态。
You have to calm down.
你必须冷静下来。
I do not believe.
我不相信。
I don't trust them at all.
我根本不信任他们。
Do you trust me?
你信任我吗？
I don't trust anyone right now.
我现在不相信任何人。
Put myself in it.
把我自己交进去。
I must surrender.
我必须自首。
Surrender
自首
is the only solution.
是唯一的解决方案。
Officials have started investigating me.
官方已经开始调查我了。
they didn't arrest you
他们没有逮捕你
This shows that Secretary Zheng did not betray you.
这说明郑书记没有背叛你。
You still have a chance.
你还有机会。
Aren’t you going to send Fang Lu abroad?
你不是要送方璐出国吗？
This is the opportunity.
这就是机会。
Send him abroad in the name of treatment.
以治疗的名义送他出国。
Considering his current situation,
考虑到他目前的状况，
he will recover soon
他很快就会康复
After treatment.
治疗后。
He is with me now,
他现在和我在一起，
How dare you poison him?
你还敢毒害他
Publicly; in public.
公开的;当众。
Once he goes abroad,
一旦他出国，
he will be
他将是
hostage
人质
In your hands.
在你的手中。
Do you think I'm a fool?
你认为我是个傻子吗？
But Fang Lu
But Fang Lu
It's a time bomb
是一颗定时炸弹
give them.
给他们。
he can
他可以
Destroy everyone at any time.
随时毁灭所有人。
Once he goes abroad,
一旦他出国，
The NSA has no reason to investigate you.
国安局没有理由调查你。
Yongping,
Yongping,
You have to trust me.
你必须相信我。
I support you.
我是支持你的。
without you,
没有你，
I wouldn't be who I am now.
我就不会是现在的我了。
If something happens to you, I'm screwed.
如果你出了什么事，我就完蛋了。
Not only me, but also Fang Lu
不仅是我，还有方璐
And a lot of people involved.
以及很多参与其中的人。
Everyone is doomed.
每个人都是注定的。
you must
你必须的
Where are you now,
你现在在哪，
Then we have hope,
然后我们就有希望，
The square road will be safe.
方路也就安全了。
If one day
如果有一天
You are under investigation,
你被调查，
We had no other choice then;
那时我们没有其他选择，
I won't be back again.
我不会再回来了。
By then, Fang Lu will be useless
到时候，方禄就没用了
give them.
给他们。
But if you surrender now
但如果你现在自首
They will definitely take revenge.
他们一定会报仇的。
Yongping, I promise you.
Yongping, I promise you.
I will protect Fang Lu.
我会保护方璐的。
I swear.
我发誓。
Yongping,
Yongping,
We don't have time.
我们没有时间。
【Emergency Internal Medicine】
【急诊内科】
[Emergency surgery]
[急诊手术]
【Blood collection room】
【采血室】
[01Emergency]
[01紧急情况]
【02Emergency】
【02紧急情况】
【03Emergency】
【03紧急情况】
PhD. Indeed.
博士。确实如此。
We've seen you before.
我们以前见过你。
Hello, doctor.
你好，医生。
【National Security Agency】
【国家安全局】
I am Gao Tianyang from the National Security Agency.
我是国家安全局的高天阳。
Please take a seat. Let's talk about it.
请坐。我们来谈谈吧。
[Spy game, start]
【间谍游戏，开始】
Something happened to Fang Lu.
方璐出事了。
Did you do it?
你做了吗？
i warned you
我警告过你
No more contacting Fang Lu.
不再联系方璐。
He came to me first.
他先来找我的。
i never
我从不
Contact him proactively.
主动联系他。
What happened today?
今天发生了什么？
He was drunk today.
他今天喝醉了。
He called me and asked me out.
他打电话给我并约我出去。
He also apologized to me
他还向我道歉
and say everything is
并说一切都是
Target him.
针对他。
I was implicated for no reason.
我无缘无故地受到了牵连。
I have no idea
我不知道
If he found something.
如果他发现了什么。
So I went there.
所以我去了那里。
Where is Huang Zicheng?
黄子成呢？
Why did he go there too?
为什么他也去了那里？
He was there when we called.
我们打电话的时候他就在那里。
He has always suspected
他一直怀疑
My relationship with Fang Lu.
我和方璐的关系。
I can't leave him behind.
我不能丢下他。
So we lived together.
所以我们就住在一起了。
What is he busy with?
他在忙什么？
He has been waiting for an interview with the biology team.
他一直在等待生物组的面试。
Anything else?
还有别的事吗？
No.
不。
I'll give you ten days.
我给你十天时间。
Huang Zicheng
Huang Zicheng
Must join the biology group.
必须加入生物组。
He has not yet attended an interview.
他还没有参加面试。
I can't guarantee this.
我不能保证这一点。
With Huang Jiaming’s status
以黄家明的地位
In the biological group,
在生物组，
I think it's not difficult
我认为这并不困难
Huang Zicheng
Huang Zicheng
Enter the biogroup.
进入生物组。
You should know
你应该知道
Consequences if you fail.
如果你失败了后果。
Also, tell Huang Zicheng.
Also, tell Huang Zicheng.
if he doesn't want to
如果他不愿意
Next Fang Lu,
下一个方璐，
show yourself.
表现自己。
Do not contact
不要联系
Fang Lu is gone.
方璐不再了。
the same as you.
你也一样。
knew.
知道了。
I am right.
我是对的。
she knows
她知道了
I went to find Fang Lu with you so quickly.
我这么快就和你一起去找方璐了。
There is only one reason.
只有一个原因。
There she is.
她就在那儿。
At the bar,
在吧台，
We didn't notice her.
我们没有注意到她。
good to know
很高兴知道
Who is Ms. Zhang?
张女士是谁。
after all,
毕竟，
She never dares to threaten us again.
她再也不敢威胁我们了。
if we knew who she was
如果我们知道她是谁
we may
我们可能
Can't survive tomorrow.
无法生存明天。
We will not be controlled by her
我们不会被她控制
all the time.
每时每刻。
The most urgent thing now
现在最紧急的事情
is to think
是要思考
How to enter the biome group.
如何进入生物组。
She has issued an ultimatum.
她已发出最后通牒。
They asked me to join the biology team
他们让我加入生物组
For my dad.
为了我爸爸。
I won't
我不会
Hurt my dad.
伤害我爸爸。
what do you want to do?
你想让我做什么？
reassure them
让他们放心
Then find a way.
然后找到方法。